

MUSAVVIR AHMED

UX ANALYST & DESIGNER

WORK EXPERIENCES

UX DESIGNER 2013-2016 Ice9 Interactive

- + Developing immersive user experience for practical uses of augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR)
- + Conducting usability tests and UX research analysis of digital products
- + Exploring new frontiers of interactive marketing

CREATIVE CONSULTANT 2014-2016 StrateGeek Digital

- + Implementing applied brand design and development
- + Supervising art in below the line (BTL) advertisements
- + Enabling innovative brand management strategies in social media

GRAPHIC DESIGNER	2013-2014
Maverick Studios	

ART DIRECTOR 2012-2013 Vibe Magazine

CONTENT SPECIALIST 2011-2012 Prothom-Alo Jobs

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an **economics** graduate from Dhaka, Bangladesh who has worked for various local businesses, playing roles ranging from junior visualizer to art director of a small time magazine, and now working as a product experience and user interface designer.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SOCIAL SCIENCE, ECONOMICS 2011-2015 **BRAC University**

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE (HSC) 2008-2010 Rifles Public College

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE (SSC) 2003-2008 Government Laboratory High School

NOTABLE WORKS

SKITTO - SELFCARE





SHOPUP - FCOMMERCE



CITYSCAPE - E-BROCHURE

BENGAL EBOI - MARKET







BEHANCE /musavvir



FACEBOOK /musavvir.info

CONTACT

House #5, Road #3, Dhanmondi-R/A, Dhaka-1205 Bangladesh

Tel. +88 017 587 36367 Web. www.musavvir.info Email. musavvir@gmail.com



DRIBBBLE /musavvir